<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetadata xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<Name>ZoopMod [StationeersMods]</Name>
	<Author>Nivvdiy</Author>
	<Version>2024.15.08</Version>
	<Description>
		[h1]ZoopMod[/h1]
		# ZoopModRecovered
		Recovered Zoop mod, which originally been made by [b]Elmotrix[/b] and advanced by [b]jixxed[/b], Mod updated from [b]Katsuk[/b] version.

		Let you build long lines of cables, pipes or chutes between two points in one action.
		Cannot make lines longer than quantity of building materials in hand.
		Can add waypoints to make cables longer

		TODO
		Make it work on client side in multiplayer.
		Make it work with Authoring tool.

		[b]Additions:[/b]
		Fix for completion time, which has been same for next building action.
		Bindable keys.
		Soft dependency for CreativeFreedom mod, give access to zooping cross devices without collision checks.
		Let you cross wires and pipes without merging, to overlap networks.
		Increase stack size for cables (250), pipes (100) and chutes (50).

		[b]Using:[/b]
		While in construction mode, hold [b]Left Shift[/b] [i](by default)[/i] and press primary action, then move mouse to zooping. hold primary to complete.
		Also can press [b]Z[/b] [i](by default)[/i] once to start zooping without hold+click.
		You can add waypoint by pressing [b]mouse middleclick[/b] [i](by default)[/i] and cancel last one with [b]V[/b] [i](by default)[/i]

		All keys can be change in stationneers settings

		# Instructions
		* If you don't have BepInEx installed, download the x64 version available at https://github.com/BepInEx/BepInEx/releases and follow the BepInEx installation instructions but basically you will need to:
		- Drop and unpack it inside Stationeers folder
		- Start the game once to finish installing BepInEx and check if he created the folders called \Stationeers\BepInEx\plugins, if yes, the BepInEx installation is completed.
		* Start the game and close again.
		* Download the last version on StationeersMods in https://github.com/jixxed/StationeersMods/releases .
		* Unpack StationeersMods inside the folder \BepInEx\plugins.
		* Subcribe in this mod on workshop steam
		* Start the game and play.

		Problems:
		Not work in Authoring mode yet.

		Works for stable version of Meson Scanner update of 2th February 2024.
		Works for stable version of Shower update of 21th March 2024

	</Description>
	<InGameDescription>
    <![CDATA[<size="30"><color=#ffa500> ZoopMod </color></size>
<b>WARNING:</b> <color=#ff0000>This is a StationeersMods Plugin Mod. It requires Bepinex to be installed with the StationeersMods plugin.</color>
See: https://github.com/jixxed/StationeersMods
 Let you build long lines of cables, pipes or chutes between two points in one action.
 Cannot make lines longer than quantity of building materials in hand.
 Can add waypoints to make cables longer

]]>
  </InGameDescription>
	<Tags />
</ModMetadata>