<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><ModMetadata xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Name>ZoopMod [StationeersMods]</Name><Author>Nivvdiy</Author><Version>2024.27.09</Version><Description>
		[h1]ZoopMod[/h1]

		[b]WARNING:[/b]
		This mod requires the StationeersMods Plugin Mod and BepInEx to be installed.
		For installation, see the detailed guide at https://github.com/jixxed/StationeersMods
		Please ensure you are unsubscribed from old versions of this mod:
		https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3182410797

		Recovered Zoop mod, originally created by [b]Elmotrix[/b] and later advanced by [b]jixxed[/b]. This mod has been updated from [b]Katsuk[/b]'s version.

		Allows you to build long lines of cables, pipes, or chutes between two points in a single action.
		Lines cannot exceed the quantity of building materials in hand.
		Waypoints can be added to extend the length of cables.

		[b]Additions:[/b]
		[list]
		[*]Fix for completion time, ensuring consistency in subsequent building actions.
		[*]Bindable keys.
		[*]Soft dependency on the CreativeFreedom mod, enabling cross-device zooping without collision checks.
		[*]Increased stack size for cables (250), pipes (100), and chutes (50).
		[/list]

		[b]Usage:[/b]
		While in construction mode, hold [b]Left Shift[/b] [i](by default)[/i] and press the primary action, then move the mouse to zoop. Hold primary to complete.
		Alternatively, press [b]Z[/b] [i](by default)[/i] once to start zooping without hold+click.
		You can add a waypoint by pressing [b]mouse middle-click[/b] [i](by default)[/i] and cancel the last one with [b]V[/b] [i](by default)[/i].

		All keys can be customized in the Stationeers settings.

		[b]TODO:[/b]
		[list]
		[*][ ]Work on client side
		[*][ ]Work with authoring tool
		[*][x]Add waypoints functionality (Version 2024.16.08)
		[*][ ]Add settings menu
		[*][ ]Add zooping for frames
		[/list]

		[b]Known Issues:[/b]
		[list]
		[*]Does not currently work in Authoring mode.
		[*]The mod is always in CreativeFreedom mode, even without the CreativeFreedom mod installed.
		[/list]

		[b]Works for:[/b]
		[list]
		[*]"Tutorials and Helper Hints" update (August 5, 2024)
		[*]"Bug Fixing" update (August 13, 2024)
		[/list]
	</Description><InGameDescription><![CDATA[<size="30"><color=#ffa500>ZoopMod</color></size>
<b>WARNING:</b> <color=#ff0000>This mod requires the StationeersMods Plugin and BepInEx to function properly.</color>
Make sure you are unsubscribed from any previous versions. Installation details are available at <b><u><color=#00ccff>https://github.com/jixxed/StationeersMods</color></u></b>.

ZoopMod allows you to build long lines of cables, pipes, or chutes between two points in a single action. Easily add waypoints to extend your construction lines without merging networks.]]></InGameDescription><Tags /></ModMetadata>